Sniper: The Last Stand is a action, thriller film
directed by Danishka Esterhazy.
To stop an arms dealer from unleashing a deadly superweapon, Ace sniper Brandon Beckett and Agent Zero are
deployed to Costa Verde to lead a group of elite soldiers against an unrelenting militia.
Taking an untested sniper under his wing, Beckett faces his newest
challenge: giving orders instead of receiving them.
With both time and ammo running low in a race to save humanity,
the team must overcome all odds just to survive.
Brandon Beckett, played by Chad Michael Collins.
Zero, played by Ryan Robbins.
Hera, played by Sharon Taylor.
Nova, played by Manuel Rodriguez-Saenz.
Modise, played by Vusi Kunene.
Zondi, played by Sizo Mahlangu.
The Last Stand is a 2013 American action thriller film starring Arnold Schwarzenegger in
his first lead acting role since Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines in 2003.
Directed by Kim Jee-woon (in his American directorial debut), the film also stars Forest Whitaker, Johnny Knoxville, Rodrigo
Santoro, Jaimie Alexander, Luis Guzmán, Eduardo Noriega, Peter Stormare, Zach Gilford, and Genesis Rodriguez.
The story sees a tough small town sheriff and his deputies attempt to stop a
dangerous drug lord from escaping to Mexico in a modified sports car.
Filming took place in Belen, New Mexico and Nevada in late 2011.
The film premiered on January 14, 2013, at Grauman's Chinese Theatre and was released on January 18, 2013, by Lionsgate
Films, receiving mixed reviews from critics and grossing $48.3 million worldwide against a $45 million budget.
The tone is intense.